From today on,
من اليوم وفصاعدا،
I'm here to rely on Master.
أنا هنا لأعتمد على المعلم.
Please take good care of me.
من فضلك اعتني بي جيدا.
Okay.
تمام.
Come on,
تعال،
wake up, young man.
استيقظ أيها الشاب.
Put away your dirty thoughts.
تخلص من أفكارك القذرة.
A new mission has appeared.
ظهرت مهمة جديدة.
Touching a beautiful girl's heart.
لمس قلب فتاة جميلة.
You must not use any coercive means.
يجب ألا تستخدم أي وسيلة قسرية.
Let Su Ying's goodwill rise to 30.
دع حسن نية Su Ying يرتفع إلى 30.
Is this also called a mission?
هل هذه تسمى أيضًا مهمة؟
Thirty is not as easy as turning over a hand.
الثلاثين ليس سهلاً مثل قلب اليد.
Master,
يتقن،
Something bad happened.
شيء ما سيء حدث.
Miss Su refused to listen to the advice and insisted on going down the mountain,
رفضت الآنسة سو الاستماع إلى النصيحة وأصرت على النزول إلى الجبل ،
what should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
Ling'er, don't panic.
Ling'er ، لا داعي للذعر.
I'm going to talk to her.
سوف أتحدث معها.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
If Miss Su goes down the mountain,
إذا نزلت الآنسة سو الجبل ،
I'm afraid she'll fall into the hands of thieves again.
أخشى أنها ستقع في أيدي اللصوص مرة أخرى.
I have to show my sincerity and persuade her to stay.
لا بد لي من إظهار إخلاصي وإقناعها بالبقاء.
Miss Su,
ملكة جمال سو ،
what do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
Me,
أنا،
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
I'm the legitimate daughter
أنا الابنة الشرعية
of the president of the Four Seas Chamber of Commerce in Falling Leaf City,
رئيس غرفة تجارة البحار الأربعة بمدينة فولنغ ليف ،
As long as you let me go,
طالما سمحت لي بالذهاب ،
the ransom won't be less than you.
لن تكون الفدية أقل منك.
Miss Su,
ملكة جمال سو ،
I don't want money,
لا اريد المال
You,
أنت،
I thought you were greedy for money,
اعتقدت أنك جشع من أجل المال ،
but I didn't expect you
لكني لم أتوقعك
to be dirty!
لتكون قذرة!
Miss Su,
ملكة جمال سو ،
let me explain.
دعني أشرح.
That's not who I am.
هذا ليس ما أنا عليه الآن.
Then what kind of person are you?
إذن أي نوع من الأشخاص أنت؟
Actually, I'm not a mountain thief,
في الواقع ، أنا لست لصًا للجبال ،
nor a robber.
ولا لص.
We are a group of self-improvement,
نحن مجموعة من تطوير الذات ،
ambitious and ambitious people,
أناس طموحون وطموحون ،
Abbreviated as
يختصر كـ
"strongman",
"رجل قوي"،
Me
أنا
The reason why I saved Miss Su up the mountain,
لماذا أنقذت الآنسة سو أعلى الجبل ،
is that I don't want her
هو أنني لا أريدها
to fall into the trap of the City Owner of Black Rock.
الوقوع في فخ مالك مدينة بلاك روك.
I know it's useless
أعلم أنه عديم الفائدة
to explain so much to Miss Su.
لشرح الكثير للآنسة سو.
Then I won't disturb Miss Su's rest.
ثم لن أزعج راحة الآنسة سو.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Master,
يتقن،
I have a plan.
لدي خطة.
It can help you out.
يمكن أن تساعدك.
In this way,
في هذا الطريق،
I'll sacrifice my own body,
سوف أضحي بجسدي ،
And then,
وثم،
in that case,
في هذه الحالة،
Thank you, Advisor.
شكرا لك مستشار.
This lady.
هذه السيدة.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm coming.
أنا قادم.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Hey,
يا،
I'm telling you, don't come near me.
أنا أخبرك ، لا تقترب مني.
Hey, hey, hey,
هلا هلا هلا،
you scream,
انت تصرخ،
Look at Master,
انظر إلى المعلم ،
how dare you lewd thief,
كيف تجرؤ على اللص البذيء ،
If you dare to touch a woman in charge,
إذا تجرأت على لمس امرأة مسؤولة ،
don't be presumptuous.
لا تكن متغطرسًا.
Qin Man,
تشين مان
alas,
واحسرتاه،
Oh,
أوه،
the boss asked me to come.
طلب مني الرئيس أن آتي.
Ouch,
أوتش ،
where are you going to escape?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب للهروب؟
I thought you were a vulgar person.
اعتقدت أنك شخص مبتذل.
I didn't expect you to be so insidious.
لم أكن أتوقع منك أن تكون غدرا جدا.
Where is Yemu Township?
أين تقع بلدة Yemu؟
The waning moon in the green hills is worrying.
القمر المتضائل في التلال الخضراء مقلق.
Why don't men take Wu Gou,
لماذا لا يأخذ الرجال Wu Gou ،
and take over the 50 states of Guanshan.
والاستيلاء على 50 ولاية من Guanshan.
When the moon is in the sky,
عندما يكون القمر في السماء ،
I thought I was the only one who felt it.
ظننت أنني الوحيد الذي شعر به.
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
that
الذي - التي
you're so literary.
أنت أدبي جدا.
Although the artistic conception doesn't match at all,
على الرغم من أن المفهوم الفني لا يتطابق على الإطلاق ،
it still rhymes.
لا تزال القوافي.
Master,
يتقن،
you are still young,
انت مازلت صغير،
I don't know what the girls are thinking.
لا أعرف ما الذي تفكر فيه الفتيات.
I have another plan,
لدي خطة أخرى ،
which can help you out.
والتي يمكن أن تساعدك.
How can you have such a useless attribute?
كيف يمكنك الحصول على مثل هذه السمة عديمة الفائدة؟
Why don't men take Wu Gou,
لماذا لا يأخذ الرجال Wu Gou ،
and take over the 50 states of Guanshan.
والاستيلاء على 50 ولاية من Guanshan.
He's not a good person,
إنه ليس شخصًا جيدًا ،
he writes good poems,
يكتب قصائد جيدة ،
It seems that he is not evil,
يبدو أنه ليس شريرًا ،
so he can only stay here for the time being.
حتى يتمكن من البقاء هنا فقط في الوقت الحالي.
Bad news.
اخبار سيئة.
Master,
يتقن،
oh, oh,
أوه أوه
bad news.
اخبار سيئة.
The army is coming.
الجيش قادم.
Ah,
آه،